from Huntsville Alabama this comes to us
從阿拉巴馬州亨茨維爾這 涉及到 我們
miss bill bill the erling game from
miss bill bill the erling game from
Huntsville Alabama I recently did a new
亨茨維爾 阿拉巴馬州 我最近做了一個新的
build it includes a rise in 720 700 X
它包括720 700 X 的增長
CPU 32 gigabytes of RAM a samsung 960
CPU 32千兆字節RAM 三星960
Evo series 500 gigabyte nvme drive and
Evo系列500千兆字節的nvme 驅動器和
Windows 10 there's a fast system yeah
Windows 10 有一個快速的系統 是啊
yeah we were talking about this
是的，我們在談論這個
yesterday and we're like I wonder what
昨天， 我們想知道是什麼
he's got there you go it's fast yeah
他到了那裡你去吧 ，快啊是的
as a retiree I'm not a heavy office user
作為退休人員，我不是一個沉重的辦公室用戶
I tried to install my old copy of MS
我試圖安裝我的舊版MS
Office and it said I had exceeded the
辦公室和它說我超過了
number of unit stalls allowed since it
自那以來允許的單位攤位數量
was AOL product I couldn't delete old
是AOL產品我無法刪除舊的
installs from the MS database I decided
我決定 從MS數據庫安裝
to install LibreOffice version 6.1 2.1
安裝LibreOffice 版本6.1 2.1
x64 the problem I have is that it takes
x64 我 遇到 的問題 是需要的
nearly 20 seconds to load I've looked at
加載了近20秒我看了
the forums and haven't found a way to
論壇和還沒有找到 一種方法 來
speed up the time it takes the load I
加快負載I所需的時間
see others also have the problem is this
看到別人也有問題 就是這個
something you could address on your
你可以解決的問題
podcast or weird on a system with 32
在32的系統上播客或怪異
gigs of ram into nvme to boot exactly
ram進入 nvme 準確 啟動
Wow
哇
because I have it on my I have it on my
因為我擁有它，我擁有它
Debian laptop right here yeah I have 8
Debian筆記本電腦就在這裡 是啊我有 8個
gigs of RAM it does have an SSD it has
它的RAM確實有它的SSD
kingston SSD and it boots up in about
金士頓SSD 和它一起開機
two and a half seconds it loads loads
兩個半 秒，它加載負荷
LibreOffice in June second and you're
6月的 LibreOffice 第二，你是
running a flavor of Linux I'm running
運行我正在運行的Linux的味道
Debian stretch now we're gonna make the
Debian伸展現在我們要做的
assumption that Bill our burlingame yes
假設 比爾我們 是伯林格姆
yeah he is probably using Microsoft
是的， 他可能正在使用微軟
Windows right yeah because we're trying
Windows 是的，因為我們正在努力
MS Office right right so I'm gonna make
MS Office右邊所以我要做
that assumption and my laptop in fact
那個假設和我的筆記本電腦其實
has Windows 10 on it so any ideas bill
有Windows 10，所以任何想法收費
okay so let's let's see if I can switch
好的，讓我們 看看我是否可以切換
over to my laptop here so that you guys
這是我的 筆記本電腦，所以你們
can see it any thoughts on this one bill
可以看到對這一條法案的任何想法
now I've got 6.1 installed so
現在我已經安裝了6.1
LibreOffice so again somebody who's
LibreOffice再次有人這樣
trying the free alternative to Microsoft
嘗試免費替代微軟
Office because of a bad situation where
辦公室因為 情況不好在哪裡
it's AOL or end-of-life so
這是AOL或者生命終結
can't call Microsoft and activate it you
不能打電話給微軟並激活 你
can't have them right yeah I mean this
不能讓他們 正確 是的我是說這個
is where you know keygens which are
是你 知道關鍵詞的地方
technically you know Shady
技術上你知道Shady
yeah that's where it's it's like oh man
是 的，這就像是男人
I paid for this product maybe that's an
我支付這個產品可能是一個
option but why is it not running fast on
選項， 但 為什麼它沒有快速運行
your system let's try it on so I'm on
你的系統讓我們嘗試一下 ，所以我在
Windows 10 on my little laptop which we
我的小筆記本電腦上的Windows 10
know is not very great and it loads
知道不是 很好 ，它加載
practically instantly the one thing that
幾乎立刻就是 那 件事
I would check is whether or not I have
我會檢查是否 有
LibreOffice Quick Start running and I
LibreOffice 快速啟動運行和我
don't I don't see a libreoffice Quick
我沒有看到一個libreoffice Quick
Start icon there so I can bring up I can
在那裡開始圖標，所以我可以調出來
bring up any LibreOffice program and hit
提出任何LibreOffice程序並點擊
tools options general and it has load
工具選項一般，它有負載
LibreOffice during system startup if I
如果我在系統啟動期間LibreOffice
hit OK on that and just so you're aware
點擊確定，就這樣你就知道了
what version I'm using here this is six
我在這裡用的是六個版本
point one point two point one so it's a
指出一點二點一，所以它是一個
match yeah so now if I close that and we
如果我關閉那個 和我們現在匹配是的
bring up to our tray
帶上我們的托盤
oh I haven't rebooted so I'm not gonna
哦， 我沒有重新啟動，所以我 不會
see it so I can force it to load right
看到它 所以我可以強制它 加載正確
now by going into my C Drive and into
現在進入 我的C盤 並進入
Program Files LibreOffice program and
程序文件LibreOffice程序和
then just do a quick I just typed qu and
那麼就快點我輸入qu和
there it is Quick Start so I'm going to
那是快速啟動， 所以我要去
double click on that and it won't appear
雙擊它，它不會出現
to have done anything but down here you
除了 你在這裡 做了什麼
see that it has in fact started and that
看到它 實際上已經 開始了
should make things a little faster now
應該讓事情變得更快一些
if I right-click on that you'll see that
如果我右鍵單擊它， 你會 看到 它
load LibreOffice during system startup
在系統啟動期間加載LibreOffice
is checked and that's because I set that
檢查，那是因為我設置了
in the options under general if you
如果您在一般選項中
don't want to go that route you can open
不想走你 可以打開的 路線
it just like I did with Program Files
就像我對Program Files一樣
LibreOffice and then right click on it
LibreOffice然後右鍵單擊它
once you've opened it and choose load
一旦你打開它並選擇加載
during system startup whether or not
在系統啟動期間是否
that will make a difference so let's try
這將有所作為讓 我們 嘗試
text document it's that's even quicker
文本文檔，它甚至更快
you could tell that that was quicker
你可以說這更快
that was instant
那是瞬間的
and it's strange because I did load it
這很奇怪因為我加載了它
on my my Windows 10 tablet last night
昨晚在我的Windows 10平板電腦上
mm-hmm and have lit a tablet and it came
mm-hmm並 點亮 了平板電腦，它來了
right on yeah two to three seconds so
是的 ， 是的 兩到三秒鐘
what could it be
會是什麼呢
yeah because not only is Bill having the
是的， 因為不僅是比爾有
phone but he says that others have had
電話，但他說其他人有
the problems as well so you found other
問題也是 如此，所以你找到了 其他的
people of like issue yeah in the forums
在 論壇中 有類似問題的人
on my computer though like now that the
我的電腦上，雖然就像現在的
quick loader quick starter is open if I
如果我，快速裝載機快速啟動器是開放的
click on text document like do you guys
像你們這樣點擊文本文檔
get the sense of how instantaneous that
得到瞬間的感覺
is I'm gonna count down from 3 so 3 2 1
我會 從 3 倒計數到 3 2 1 1
click so it's very very quick now no
點擊這樣它現在非常快
delay whatsoever if I do it from I
如果我從 我這裡 做的話會拖延
wouldn't be fast enough to start the
不會快到足以啟動
stopwatch yeah so that's that does make
秒錶耶， 所以這確實
a difference online a market difference
市場差異在線差異
although mine didn't seem slow in the
雖然我的似乎並不慢
first place but it is very much faster
第一名但速度要快得多
now I'd suggest that you try that bill
現在我建議 你試試這個賬單
any other suggestions or anything else
任何其他建議或其他任何
that you can think of I think QuickStart
你能想到的，我認為 快速入門
is the first place I would looking
是我會 找 首位
absolutely yeah absolutely and
絕對是的，絕對是
unfortunately some of the forums and
不幸的是一些論壇和
some of the if you did a Google search
如果您進行Google 搜索 ，則會有一些問題
they give you advice on older versions
他們會為您提供舊版本的建議
of LibreOffice oh and it yes it tells
LibreOffice哦 ，是的它告訴我
you to go to tools options memory which
你去工具 選項 記憶哪個
doesn't exist anymore oh okay it was
不存在了 哦好吧它
deprecated in 5.4 I believe or something
在5.4中我不相信或不相信
like that right well if and so maybe
如果可能的話， 那就 好了
they move things around so maybe it's
他們移動東西所以也許就是這樣
important just to make that mental note
這個 心理記錄非常重要
that you can go in to see colon slash
你可以進去看結腸斜線
Program Files slash libreoffice /
程序文件斜杠libreoffice /
software slash quickstart and run that
軟件斜杠快速入門並運行它
program it'll load it into the tray
程序它將它 加載到 托盤中
right-click on it and go low at startup
右鍵單擊它並 在 啟動時 變低
and they make that mental note yeah you
並且他們做了那個心理記錄，是的
got that locked in I hope that helps
得到了鎖定 我希望有所幫助
bill please let us know if that makes
請告訴我們
any difference but your computer sounds
任何差異，但你的電腦聽起來
amazing
驚人
sounds like you should not be
聽起來你不應該
experiencing that issue not probable so
遇到這個問題的可能性不大
let us know all right
讓我們知道
[Music]
[音樂]
[Applause]
[掌聲]